Complementing the previous video and taking advantage of the fact that we are in the
another time other than the arms race, there is something very interesting
that I want to show you here.
When it comes to the drone tax segment, people think of choking
resources with drone, but it is not interesting to spend resources with drone.
There's another secret here. The secret of this tab is the use of vigor.
So, as you can see, I need to get up to 30,000 points here.
And to get to 30,000 points, the easiest way using vigor,
spending 300 of vigor, but then you're thinking,
Luís, how am I going to spend 300 of vigor, where I'm going to get 300 of vigor.
Then I say calm, first thing, people.
It's you coming here to the covenant store.
In the VIP store, you can buy vigor.
It has a limit, but you can buy it.
And you also have to keep track of time to be able to restart.
You already do it again, it will be a certain specific day that you make
hallway. So, you program yourself for that.
Another place you can buy vigor.
Here, without vigor, then you say, wow, 300 diamonds to buy vigor.
But you have to understand that we buy 300,
without vigor with 300 diamonds, but we also gain 50 vigor.
Gains 100 stamina twice a day.
50 of vigor twice a day.
Only then it's 200, but what you get from equilinology.
Then, what is interesting that people don't notice?
It's just that, in our faces, we already win, if we add everything up,
here you get 50, but 150, 350 diamonds.
Only from here, are the fragments and universal recruitment tickets.
The hero universal fragments and the tickets.
Calm down, who else has it?
If you spend 300, you have to spend 300 what?
On the battlefield, correct?
So, we come here to the world.
In the world, we still have another situation,
which is what we have an area task that is to defeat 5 zombies.
You defeat 5 zombies without giving a medal.
In addition to having these other missions, which each give a little diamond.
If we're going to do the zombies, in addition to buying the area task,
we can make a zombie attack of a slight or maximum that we haven't reached yet.
But it's already 70.
So, you get a lot of diamond here.
You attack 4 normal zombies, then you go and pass to the side to attack the last level.
Also, guys, we still have D1 Elite.
But you spent 50 stamina.
What's missing is 13 attacks in D1 Elite.
But you can see that D1 Elite can also give you diamonds.
Besides, I've already killed some of an Elite here.
I didn't get a diamond, but look at that.
I won tickets and recruits, and I won accelerators that are very important for you to pass the level faster.
Because waiting for the construction by itself ends up hindering us
is still developing.
Another thing I want to take advantage of is that since I have the unit progression event,
at two o'clock in the morning, and here it's 15 and 35,
how do I program myself?
There are practically 10 hours left to be able to collect.
So what do I do?
I put my soldiers for me to attack in 1 or 2 hours.
Because then, all of them are over, I go and put in 8 hours left.
That then I can collect exactly on time,
in which the corretarmamentista's event regarding unit progression will take place.
Right?
So, do not be afraid to spend, vigor and buy things where lover.
Wearing diamonds is important for you to achieve your goals.
And at this time of day, it's a great time for you to score well.
You got 30,000 points in the corretarmamentista and still win a lot of other things at that time.
In addition to being good for you to evolve lightly,
you still get many other things that will make the SU team much stronger.
Your heroes get stronger.
So, open your eye and take this tip.